[×](javascript:void(0)) [MENU](#)

Use of Data
===========

Speed Of Me, LLC ("SERVICE") ensures that the personal data of individuals that visit our homepage are protected pursuant to the applicable law of the United States and is compliant with the EU's General Data Protection Act as regards the use of personal data for EU residents while located in the EU. SERVICE has implemented all measures that might be required to ensure the protection of personal data and to prevent unauthorized disclosure thereof to third parties. Nevertheless, the SERVICE shall not undertake responsibility for other homepages linked to our site, or for services of other parties accessible via our website.

Information about visitors that becomes known to us as a result of their use of our homepage is processed according to the intended purpose, e.g. to provide the requested information or services.

To be able to provide services and decide about the necessity of improving the layout or content of our homepage, information about its visitors that we have collected in the access files, e.g. IP address, Internet provider, access timing, and the viewed sections is also processed. If the Internet speed gauge is used, we process the measured result.

We use cookies as they provide for a better functionality of our site. The technologies that we use allow to refuse cookies, but it is not recommended, as it will limit the functionality of our website available to you. The Cookies Policy is available [here](#cookies).

Processing of personal data by SERVICE
--------------------------------------

SPEED OF ME, LLC as a controller or processor of personal data processing carries out the processing of personal data and ensures their protection in accordance with the laws and regulations on the protection of data processing. Everybody can freely choose - to give or not to give consent to the processing of his/her personal data, and at any time easily and conveniently, by [contacting us](mailto:support@speedof.me?subject=Data%20Removal%20Request&body=Name:%20%0AMy%20IP%20Address:%20x.x.x.x%20%0ADate/Time%20Website%20Accessed:), to withdraw the consent, without affecting the processing done before the withdrawal. Likewise every person may exercise the rights of data subjects stipulated in the laws and regulations, including the right to receive information on his/her data, to object against the processing, including the use of legitimate interests, as well as to submit an application on the rectification, deletion, restriction and transferring of data, to give his/her opinion and to ask to review the decision adopted within the automated process, as well as in case of need to submit a complaint to the supervisory institutions regarding personal data protection issues.  
  
TO CHANGE CONSENT OR RECEIVE INFORMATION ON DATA YOU MUST PROVIDE THE IP ADDRESS WITH THE DATE AND TIME THIS WEBSITE WAS ACCESSED. THIS IS THE ONLY WAY WE TRACK OR STORE INFORMATION AND WITHOUT THE ABOVE INFORMATION WE CANNOT RETRIEVE RECORDS.

* * *

Privacy Policy
==============

Our Privacy Policy was last updated and posted on July 22, 2019. It governs the privacy terms of our Website, located at [https://speedof.me/privacy.html](https://speedof.me/privacy.html). Any capitalized terms not defined in our Privacy Policy, have the meaning as specified in our [Terms of Service](https://speedof.me/terms.html).

Check out our Ad partner privacy policy [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/speedof.me).

Your Privacy
------------

SPEED OF ME, LLC follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section below.

Definitions
-----------

"Non Personal Information" is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser. It may also include publicly available information that is shared between you and others.

"Personally Identifiable Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you within our Website. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your name, email address, ISP and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you.

Information We Collect
----------------------

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website.

As a Visitor, you can browse our website to find out more about our Website. You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor.

Computer Information Collected
------------------------------

When you use our Website, we automatically collect certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website and such information is typically considered Non Personal Information. We also collect the following:

* #### Cookies
    
    Our Website uses "Cookies" to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.
    
    The following Cookies may be used on the website:
    
    * Technical or strictly necessary Cookies allow you to freely open and browse the website and enjoy its functionality, including the ability to receive information about services and purchase them. However, we will not be able to satisfy your requests. The website will remember to which Cookies you have consented.
        
    * Analytics Cookies compile information about your use of the website and your favorite sections, including the content that you open, when you browse the site. Information is used in aggregate form for analytical purposes. Third party Cookies, e.g. Google Analytics Cookies, may also be used.
        
* #### Automatic Information
    
    We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you're headed when you leave our website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

We use the information we receive from you as follows:

* #### Customizing Our Website
    
    We may use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to customize our Website.
    
* #### Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties
    
    We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide services to us with regards to our Website (i.e. payment processors, Website hosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.
    
* #### Data Aggregation
    
    We retain the right to collect and use any Non Personal Information collected from your use of our Website and aggregate such data for internal analytics that improve our Website and Service as well as for use or resale to others. At no time is your Personally Identifiable Information included in such data aggregations.
    
* #### Legally Required Releases of Information
    
    We may be legally required to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of SPEED OF ME, LLC, our Users, employees, and affiliates.

Privacy Policy Updates
----------------------

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we may notify you on our Website, by a blog post, by email, or by any method we determine. The method we chose is at our sole discretion. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.
